The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
A handprint ?
A single hand damaged the gate of the Celestial Realm so much ?
This must have been a very large platform before...
But some kind of fight
shattered it to this extent.
How powerful was that spell ?
First, I need to set up a restriction
as well as a recovery formation.
If I get hurt in the Celestial Realm,
after coming out,
I can always come back here to recover.
I didn't expect a platform could be this useful.
Move aside !
Fellow cultivator,
please leave this platform
and find another one.
He's... from the Giant Demon Clan ?
Chi Hu\NGiant Demon Clan's young master\NMiddle stage Soul Formation
Late stage Soul Formation ?
Please forgive me.
He is very strong.
Sun Tai\NCorpse Sect Head Elder\NMiddle stage Soul Transformation
I can't offend him.
Junior Brother,
come with me.
Zhou Yi\NFive Elements Sect disciple\NMiddle stage Soul Transformation
Why him ?
He's disgusting.
I need to find someone with a low cultivation level.
Zhai Ban\NEarly stage Soul Formation
Early stage Soul Formation...
But I can't underestimate
his domain.
This guy will be hard to deal with.
Why don't
I choose him instead ?
Fellow cultivator,
please leave this platform
and find another one.
Then don't blame me for being rude !
This is...
A Thunder Toad !
Have I...
seen him somewhere before ?
The Return Cauldron,
can be activated
at certain locations
and after an incense stick of time
it allows you to leave the Celestial Realm
and return to your cultivation planet.
Is this
the Celestial Realm ?
Rain Celestial Realm
This one will do.
Spirit stones ?
Could it be that this whole palace
is made of spirit stones ?
What a pity...
When it was at its prime,
how grand must this place have been.
The celestial spiritual energy
is countless times purer than regular spiritual energy.
Since the Celestial Realm is shattered,
celestial spiritual energy
is very scarce.
What kind of spell
could have destroyed this place ?
What happened in the Celestial Realm back then ?
A few days later
"Gifted by the fifth Rain Celestial Emperor
to Celestial Scholar Tian Hua..."
This celestial palace is so luxurious !
It must have belonged
to a Celestial King !
This tablet should have been outside to allow people to read it.
But now it's hidden deep inside the palace.
Weird...
There's a restriction here !
Celestial spiritual energy !
The celestial spiritual energy
must be condensed with an Origin Soul
into jades
to be used later.
Stop !
Hong Wen\NDa Lou Sword Sect\NEarly stage Soul Formation
This place was discovered 3000 years ago by the Da Lou Sword Sect.
If you continue,
the Da Lou Sword Sect
will kill you !
Thunder...
Thunder Toad !
Ridiculous.
When did your sect
become the owner of the Celestial Realm ?
Go !
The Da Lou sword
is one of the top artifacts of the Da Lou Sword Sect.
Cultivators of the same level
cannot withstand its attacks.
This person is clearly Early stage Soul Formation
but his Thunder Toad
is as strong as a Middle stage Soul Formation.
Who is this guy ?
The Celestial Realm is shattered.
Although the formation of this palace has been mostly destroyed,
it's still somewhat operational.
Given enough time,
it will automatically gather scattered celestial spiritual energy
and condense it here.
After the Da Lou Sword Sect discovered this,
you hid it beneath this tablet
and you come here regularly
to harvest it.
Am I... wrong ?
No.
I am not his match.
Such a small jade
is equivalent to almost half of Zhao's spiritual energy
if it was all combined.
For now,
I can only try my best
to stall him.
You just wait !
I will find my Senior Brother,
and we will kick your ass.
You will never be able to get out of the Celestial Realm !
Running away ?
Teleportation formations in the Celestial Realm ?
This sect is a big deal.
You rat...
Don't you know I'm Soul Formation ?
As long as the Origin Soul lives
the body is eternal !
We're at the same stage,
you can't kill me.
You just wait for my Senior Brother to arrive.
This is a refining bell,
an ancient artifact that can trap people and refine them.
It's only a matter of time
before your Origin Soul dies.
I beg you,
listen to me !
Let me go !
I will give you my Soul Blood !
Too late...
Once we get his bag of holding,
we will be able to use the teleportation formations
of the Da Lou Sword Sect.
Master, you are so smart !
Refining his Origin Soul will take time.
This matter cannot be rushed.
A few days later
It's a pity that these thousand-years old trees
are all dead.
If I could use those trees
for wood carving,
who knows how powerful it could be.
This is...
a Celestial's cave ?
Although this cave is empty,
there are many restrictions here
that are useful to me.
Once the 9999th restriction is complete,
the Restriction Flag
will be upgraded again.
Save me
This mountain has existed for a long time.
I am not the first person to find this.
How can this place
still exist ?
Even if a Celestial is locked up down there,
it's not something I can deal with.
3 days later
The time has come.
This is...
So many top-quality spirit stones !
Master,
we're rich now !
You rat,
accept your fate !
You... were prepared for it ?
If I didn't want to keep this sword,
you wouldn't even have had time to act.
This sword has hundreds of restrictions carved on it.
It's somewhat similar to my Restriction Flag.
Our Da Lou Sword Sect
found 37 fragments of the Celestial Realm.
Each of them has a teleportation formation.
By holding this jade
and using spirit stones, one can activate the formations
to travel between them at will.
This jade is very important,
it must not fall into the hands of outsiders.
This place is completely destroyed.
I don't feel any celestial spiritual energy.
So why did they
set up the teleportation formation here ?
Hurry up !
Someone's here ?
Okay, I got it.
I don't know how many Celestials will come this year.
Celestials ?
They look real
but I can't feel any Life energy from them.
I think it's some kind of illusion.
This is...
A Celestial Palace of the past ?
Ye Jiu,
you can't escape today, come.
Stop.
This year's Celestial fruit is extra sweet.
Yesterday, Celestial Bi Bo invited me to play a song together.
How is that possible ?
Let's get drunk !
Cheers !
Sister, one more dance.
It's as if heaven and earth are in their hands.
They can bend it at will
in an infinite number of ways.
Is this a celestial spell ?
The Celestial Realm is strong.
How was it destroyed ?
Who's trespassing in the Celestial Realm !?
A palm ?
Fight back !
This palm strike
can move mountains and split the seas.
Little sister !
Although this palm is an illusion,
I can still learn from it.
One move.
The Celestial Realm was destroyed in one move !
Falling from the night sky and melting into dust\Nlike water without a source.
Like the difference between clouds and mud,\Nthe truth cannot be found in conflict.
Life and death\Nare like the moment when the rain falls
and like many other unseparable things.
In this lifetime,\Nto cultivate the truth, cultivate the world first.
Old grudges had to be settled\Nbecause half an inch is engraved into my tree rings.
Use the most vivid love and hate\Nto ask questions to your fate.
Let your eyes be filled enough with rage\Nto pierce the heart and the soul
then soften because of the mortals' fireworks.
Only when you bend down can you understand\Nthe hidden edge of the blade.
The human mind is nature,\Nthe rain fell silently like an answer.
Life and death are just moments away,\Nthere are many other solutions to grudges.
Use your dusty heart\Nto depict the world.
One stroke is for killing.\NAfter struggling for hundreds of years, I endured letting go.
One stroke is for caring.\NEverywhere there is life, there are thousands of lights.
Give up your mind to be refined\Nby this endless world.
The human mind is nature,\Nthe rain fell silently like an answer.
Life and death are just moments away,\Nthere are many other solutions to grudges.
Use your dusty heart\Nto depict the world.
One stroke is for killing.\NAfter struggling for hundreds of years, I endured letting go.
One stroke is for caring.\NEverywhere there is life, there are thousands of lights.
Give up your mind to be refined\Nby this endless world.
Snow falls as my hair turns white, winter withers\Nwhile prosperity sprouts in summer.
I step into the world, with light at my fingertips,\Nthe law of cause and effect.
I observe the vastness of heaven and earth so I can get rid of evil.
Obsession arises from one thought, life and death arise from one thought.\NReincarnation is not to be feared.